Everybody’s Everything is a documentary film directed by Ramez Silyan.
The story of artist Lil Peep from his birth in Long Island and meteoric rise as a genre blending pop star &
style icon, to his death due to an accidental opioid overdose in Arizona at just 21 years of age.
Self, played by Lil Peep.
Self, played by Lil Tracy.
Self, played by GHOSTEMANE.
Self, played by Killstation.
Self, played by Bexey.
Self, played by Juicy J.
Everybody's Everything is a 2019 documentary film about
the life of American rapper Lil Peep.
The film was directed by Sebastian Jones and Ramez Silyan, produced by Benjamin Soley and
executive produced by Terrence Malick, Liza Womack and Sarah Stennett.
It chronicles the life of Lil Peep from his childhood in Long Beach, NY through his meteoric rise in the
underground scene and music industry, up to his death on November 15, 2017 at the age of 21.
The film takes its title from one of Lil Peep's Instagram
posts, which appeared the day before his death.
“I just wanna be everybody's everything," he wrote.
The documentary is described as a "humanistic portrait that seeks to understand an artist who attempted to be all things to all people."
The film had its world premiere at South by
Southwest on March 10, 2019 and was released by Gunpowder & Sky for one-night worldwide fan screenings on November 12 ahead of its theatrical release on November 15, 2019.
A companion album of the same name was released by Columbia
Records alongside the film on November 15, 2019.
The film explores themes of biography, drug overdose,
nostalgic, candid, portrait of an artist.